const STORE = [
  {
    question: `Who is the founder of Marvel?`,
    answers: [
      `Martin Goodman`,
      `Stan Lee`,
      `Peter Parker`,
      `Walt Disney`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Martin Goodman`,
  },
  {
    question: `Who has the ability to control metals?`,
    answers: [
      `Moving-Guy`,
      `Magnet-Man`,
      `Magneto`,
      `Mario`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Magneto`,
  },
  {
    question: `Which superhero is not part of the Marvel Universe?`,
    answers: [
      `Iron Man`,
      `Captain America`,
      `Wolverine`,
      `Batman`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Batman`,
  },
  {
    question: `Who told Peter Parker (Spiderman) “With great power comes great responsibility?`,
    answers: [
      `Aunt Mae`,
      `Thor`,
      `Uncle Ben`,
      `Bruce Banner`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Uncle Ben`,
  },
  {
    question: `Peter Parker works as a photographer for:`,
    answers: [
      `The New York Times`,
      `The Post`,
      `The Daily Bugle`,
      `The Daily Planet`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `The Daily Bugle`,
  },
  {
    question: `The Thing is a member of which team?`,
    answers: [
      `X-men`,
      `The Liberators`,
      `The Fantastic Four`,
      `The Power Rangers`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `The Fantastic Four`,
  },
  {
    question: `Who is the main villain in the 2018 Marvel’s Avengers Infinity War movie?`,
    answers: [
      `Thanos`,
      `Braniac`,
      `Darkseid`,
      `Lex Luthor`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Thanos`,
  },
  {
    question: `Who is the crowned prince of Asgard?`,
    answers: [
      `Black Panther`,
      `Daredevil`,
      `Thor`,
      `Vision`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Thor`,
  },
  {
    question: `What state in the USA Peter Parker, Jessica Jones, Matt Murdock and Luke Cage reside?`,
    answers: [
      `Virginia`,
      `Gotham City`,
      `New York`,
      `New Jersey`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `New York`,
  },
  {
    question: `What kind of metal Wolverine’s skeleton plated?`,
    answers: [
      `Titanium`,
      `Tungsten`,
      `Material X`,
      `Adamantium`
    ],
    correctAnswer: `Adamantium`,
  }
];